<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KNWLDG</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="about_us">What is KNWLDG?</string>
    <string name="about_us_description">KNWLDG is an educational application that spread general knowledge about Malaysia thought playing interaction game</string>
    <string name="vision">What is KNWLDG\&apos; Vision?</string>
    <string name="vision_desc">The vision of our company is to make future learning more interesting and diverse</string>
    <string name="objective">What is KNWLDG\&apos; objective?</string>
    <string name="objective_desc">The objective of our company is to develop a general knowledge e-learning mobile application that are suitable for every age group, especially ranging from kindergarten kids to teenagers</string>

    <string-array name="malaysia_facts">
        <item>Malaysia lies close to the equator and thus has an equatorial climate with two rainy seasons. The humidity is very high.</item>
        <item>Singapore is linked to Johor Bahru/Malaysia by a 26 km/ 16 miles long bridge.</item>
        <item>Malaysia\&apos;s highest point is Mount Kinabalu, which is on the island of Borneo. Mount Kinabalu is 4,095 m/ 13,435 ft high.</item>
        <item>The longest river is the Rajang river with 563 km/ 350 ft.</item>
        <item>Malaysia has 13 states, the biggest state called Sarawak and the smallest is Perlis. </item>
        <item>Malaysia has hundreds of islands along the coastline. Pulau Langkawi is the biggest island of the country. </item>
        <item>Malaysia is slightly larger in area than the state of New Mexico/USA or slightly larger than Norway.</item>
        <item>East Malaysia is on the island of Borneo and consists of two states: Sabah and Sarawak.</item>
        <item>Peninsular Malaysia is linked to Singapore by a causeway and a bridge.</item>
        <item>Singapore, China, the USA and Japan are Malaysia\&apos;s main export and import partners.</item>
        <item>The population in rural East Malaysia lives in typical long houses.</item>
        <item>Malaysia is among the seventeen megadiverse countries. This means there is extremely high biodiversity in Malaysia.</item>
        <item>The island of Borneo is not only the largest island in Asia, but the third largest island in the world!</item>
        <item>The Sultanate of Kedah on the Malay Peninsula is one of the oldest in the world, established in A.D. 1136.</item>
        <item>Some buildings in Malaysia do not have a fourth floor. They are replaced by \&apos;3A\&apos; as the sound of four (sì) is similar to the sound of death in Chinese (sĭ).</item>
        <item>In Malaysia, a heart bypass surgery can be done for approximately US$9,000. The same operation costs around $130,000 in the U.S.</item>
        <item>According to the World Tourism Organization (WTO), Malaysia has developed into the ninth most visited country in the world, with 23.6 million visitors in 2009.</item>
        <item>Orangutan is humans\&apos; closest relative and Asia’s only great ape. Orangutans can be found only in the wild in Borneo and Sumatra.</item>
        <item>Seventeen-year-old Kok Shoo Yin became the first Malaysia citizen certificate holder when he received his official documentation on November 14, 1957.</item>
        <item>Found in 1991, Perak Man is the oldest (about 11,000 years old) and the only complete human skeleton to be found in Peninsular Malaysia.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="terms">
       By accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any part of the terms then you may not access the Service.\n

        \nContent\n
        Our Service allows you to post, link, store, share and otherwise make available certain information, text, graphics, videos, or other material (\&apos;Content\&apos;). You are responsible for the …\n

        \nChanges\n
        We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material we will try to provide at least 30 (change this) days\&apos; notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.\n

        \nContact Us\n
        If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us.\n
    </string>

    <string name="rules">
        1. KNWLDG is a multiple choice question game.\n\n
        2. You are required to read and study the tutorial before starting the game.\n\n
        3. Choose only one answer and click "CONFIRM" button to submit your answer.\n\n
        4. You have 15 seconds to answer each question.\n\n
        5. Purchased boost can be activated in the game.\n\n
        6. Each correct answer will be rewarded with 20 eCoins.\n\n
        7. Wrong answer will be rewarded with nothing.\n\n
        8. You need to score more than or equal to 50% (100 eCoins) to pass and collect the reward.\n\n
    </string>

</resources>